You
そなた
Come with me
俺についてこい
You two
二人とも
Hand over your weapons
武器を置き
Follow my soldiers
我が兵とともに進め
Of course, of course
承知いたしました
We will follow the general's orders
将軍のご命令に従います
Mount up
下馬しろ！
Your Highness
殿下
General Shilang already knows
石狼将軍はすでに承知仕りおわす
That this time the Xuan army went north
今回、宣軍北上は
Was
晋王殿下の
Promoted entirely by Prince of Jin
一己の志と聞き
For Prince of Jin
殿下の
To have such courage
ご胆力に
He deeply admires
深く感服され
Saying Your Highness
彼は
In the future
日後
Will surely be Xuan Kingdom's new ruler
必ず宣国の新主とならんと存じ候
General Shilang
石狼将軍
Wishes to befriend Your Highness
殿下との交誼を望み
Both sides cease fighting
両軍は休戦し
And each gets what they need, how about it?
互いの益を取ることはいかがか？
Then tell me
ほう、それで？
What does Shilang need?
石狼将軍が何を願い
And what do I need?
我らが何を得ると申すか？
General Shilang
石狼将軍
Is willing to give
弋陽城を
Yiyang City
殿下に献ずる
To Your Highness
用意がござる
But
されど
When Your Highness ascends the throne
将来、即位の折には
Please appoint
石狼将軍を
General Shilang
鎮北王に
As Prince Zhenbei
封じ
And grant the prosperous land of Qing Province
豊饒の地・慶州を
As his domain
彼の領地と為し給え
What a deal
良い商売じゃ
To trade our Xuan city
我ら宣国の城を差し出し
For our Xuan province
我らの州を与うると申すか？
General, please don't be angry
将軍、どうぞ憤り給わぬよう
Let me finish speaking
最後までお聞きくだされ
That year
かつて
General Shilang
石狼将軍
Was the first to enter Yong'an
最初に永安城を入り
By chance
その際
He obtained a great treasure
偶々得し至宝がござる
This treasure
その玉
Green as blue in color
翠色に映え
Smooth and square
形正しく
With a jade chi-tiger knob
螭虎（りこ）の玉紐をもつるは
Is precisely our Xuan Kingdom's
正に
Imperial seal
宣国の――伝国璽にございます
What?
なに？
How could that be?
まさか
What a reversal of truth
何とぞ倒錯せし論か――
Invading our country
我が都を攻めしことを
Is said to be entering Yong'an
「永安城に入る」と言い
Massacring the entire court
文武百官を斬り
Stealing the seal
伝国璽を奪い
Is said to be by chance
それを「偶々至宝を得し」
Obtaining a great treasure
と申すか？
You, a Xuan person
そなたは宣人にて
Acting as a dog under the enemy
敵に仕えし狗奴
Dare to speak nonsense
何を戯言ほざくか
Believe it or not
今
I'll kill you right now
ここ斬り捨てんぞ覚悟あるか
Your Highness
殿下！
This official wouldn't dare
許せ給え！
This official absolutely wouldn't dare
下官は断じて
To risk my own head
命を賭し
As a joke
冗談しつもりはなく候！
If Your Highness is interested
殿下はご興味あらば
You can wait until tonight
今宵
The seal
城中へ伝国璽を
Will be sent into the city
お運び仕り候